All you had to do was pay us enough to live
Said the man behind the can before the flame was lit
Push come to shove, come from above to where the labor lives
Down on the bottom, but the problem's where the board members sit
Executives, a ruling class that laps in caste system
I need to deck them in the halls
They never see the people coming even when they from us
Never feel the power humming because it's from within us
Indigenous, our talk thinnest
Ruled by the moon, before the dollar was the idol
Before there was a bible, before we were trained to walk single file
And pledge allegiance to politicians
Communal living, I hope you're listening, I hope you're listening
Cause buddy with that lighter at the end of his rope
Will do more than murder, cause the supply chain choke
That warehouse was a burial ground of desire
Futures flew free as the flames grew higher
Higher, higher, higher as the flames grew